Finding Aid for the Susan Sontag Papers LSC.0612
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 9: Bosnia Involvement, 1979-2002
  - Sub-series 9.1, 1979-2002; 4 boxes (2.00 lin. ft.)
    - Letters from The Republic of Bosnia & Hezogovina., 1994 October 17. (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Refugees International., 1993-1994. (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Oslobodenje-Onasa., no date. (Box 107, Folder 11)
      ca. 40 pages.
    - Nermina Kurspahic., 2000-2002. (Box 107, Folder 12)
      40 pages.
    - Sarajevo letters., 1993-1994. (Box 107, Folder 13)
      ca. 85 pages.
    - Bosnia letters., 1993-1999. (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - Fall of Yugoslavia (The) map., no date. (Box 117, Folder 1)
      1 item. Container 117 is an oversize map folder
    - Miro - Witnesses of Existence., 1993-1994. (Box 165, Folder 1)
      ca. 120 pages and 13 items.
    - Simic family immigration., 1995-1996. (Box 165, Folder 2)
      Folder 1 of 2. ca. 130 pages.
    - Simic family immigration., 1995-1996. (Box 165, Folder 3)
      Folder 2 of 2. ca. 150 pages.
    - Amela and Goran Simic., 1994-2002. (Box 165, Folder 4)
      92 items. Includes typescript manuscript with holograph corrections of Goran Simic's short fiction/poetry collection "Sarajevo Sorrow" and holograph manuscript of Sontag's foreword.
    - Art Spiegelmann, Children's Letters & Drawings., 1993. (Box 165, Folder 5)
      ca. 120 pages.
    - I Dream of Peace book., no date. (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - Honorary Citizen of Sarajevo proclamation., 1993 August 17. (Box 165, Folder 7)
    - Akademija Scenskih Umjetnosti, paperback book., 1992. (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - First trip to Sarajevo, April 1993. (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Bosnia letters., 1995-2002. (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence with Senada Kreso regarding Annie Leibovitz photograph of Haris Silajdzic., 1995-1996. (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - Prague: People in Need., 1996. (Box 166, Folder 5)
      42 pages.
    - Bosnian Elegies by Adrian Oktenberg., 1996. (Box 166, Folder 6)
      68 pages.
  - Sub-series 9.2, 1993-2000; 1.5 boxes (0.75 lin. ft.)
    Documents and correspondence regarding Sontag and her sponsorship of the Gluhic family immigration to the United States from Sarajevo.
    - ., 1995. (Box 106, Folder 1)
      INS Documents. 63 pages.
    - ., 1993-1995. (Box 106, Folder 2)
      Hasan Gluhic. Ca. 120 pages.
    - ., 1995. (Box 106, Folder 3)
      Amela Simic correspondence regarding Hasan Gluhic. 13 pages.
    - ., 1994-1995. (Box 106, Folder 4)
      Documents. Folder 1 of 4. 26 pages.
    - ., 1994-1995. (Box 106, Folder 5)
      Documents. Folder 2 of 4. ca. 120 pages.
    - ., 1994-1995. (Box 106, Folder 6)
      Documents. Folder 3 of 4. ca. 150 pages.
    - ., 1994-1995. (Box 106, Folder 7)
      Documents. Folder 4 of 4. ca. 130 pages.
    - ., 1994-1995. (Box 106, Folder 8)
      Asylum documents and correspondence. ca. 150 pages.
    - ., 1994-1995. (Box 106, Folder 9)
      Supplementary information. 3 items and 16 pages.
    - ., 1994-1995. (Box 106, Folder 10)
      Lottery. 23 pages.
    - ., no date. (Box 106, Folder 11)
      Employment authorization. 4 pages.
    - ., no date. (Box 106, Folder 12)
      Birthday cards. 4 items.
    - ., 1994. (Box 107, Folder 1)
      Helena Kane Finn and Leon Wieseltier. 14 pages.
    - ., 1994. (Box 107, Folder 2)
      Advance parole and Croation Visa. ca. 30 pages.
    - ., 1995. (Box 107, Folder 3)
      Lazar Stojanoric. ca. 50 pages.
    - ., 1995. (Box 107, Folder 4)
      Naida and Tarik: school. Folder 1 of 3. 16 pages.
    - ., 1997, 1999-2000. (Box 107, Folder 5)
      Naida and Tarik: school. Folder 2 of 3. ca. 110 pages.
    - ., no date. (Box 107, Folder 6)
      Naida and Tarik: school. Folder 3 of 3. 2 items and 7 pages.
    - ., 1994. (Box 107, Folder 7)
      Miscellaneous. 3 items and ca. 60 pages.
  - Sub-series 9.3, 1992-1996; 2 boxes (1.00 lin. ft.) and 2 oversize folders
    News from and about Bosnia.
    - Newsletters., 1992-1995. (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - ., ca. 1993-1996. (Box 164, Folder 20)
      ca. 100 items. All material found within the collection and grouped together by UCLA. Includes photographs
    - ., 1995. (Box 164, Folder 21)
      ca. 20 items.
    - Bosnian newsletters and newspapers., 1993-1995. (Box 166, Folder 7)
    - Magazines., 1992-1996. (Box 166, Folder 8)
    - Weekly Review CHC., 1995. (Box 166, Folder 9)
    - CSCE News Release., 1994 February 10. (Box 166, Folder 10)
    - Bosnia., 1996. (Box 166, Folder 11)
      ca. 50 items.
    - ., 1994. (Box 166, Folder 12)
      ca. 80 items.
    - ., 1994-1995. (Box 166, Folder 13)
      ca. 33 items.
    - ., 1993-1996. (Box 167)
      5 folders. ca. 500 items.
    - ., ca. 1993-1996. (Box 168, Folder 1)
      ca. 100 items.
    - Newspapers., 1993. (Box 302, Folder 5)
- Series 10: PEN Involvement, 1964-2003
  Correspondence, documents, and printed material relating to Sontag's PEN membership and term as president. See also "Public Activity" and "Political Activity" series.
  - ., 1964, 1981-1998, 2002. (Box 72, Folder 1)
    Newsletters and news releases. 13 items.
  - ., 1965, 1984-1989. (Box 72, Folder 2)
    Press. 15 items.
  - ., 1990. (Box 72, Folder 3)
    Steinberg. 28 pages.
  - ., 1977, 1987-1999. (Box 72, Folder 4)
    Events. 26 items.
  - ., 1987-1989. (Box 72, Folder 5)
    International. ca. 100 pages.
  - ., 1981-2000. (Box 72, Folder 6)
    American Center. 136 pages.
  - ., 1987-1989. (Box 72, Folder 7)
    Executive Board rosters, correspondence, and meeting agendas. 49 pages.
  - ., 1987-1997. (Box 72, Folder 8)
    Executive Board meetings. 127 pages.
  - ., 1991-1993. (Box 73, Folder 1)
    Yugoslavia. ca. 150 pages.
  - ., 1989-1991. (Box 73, Folder 2)
    Salman Rushdie. 147 pages.
  - ., 1989-1990. (Box 73, Folder 3)
    Salman Rushdie Affair articles. 24 items.
  - ., 1997-2000. (Box 73, Folder 4)
    The Writer, the Work. ca. 100 pages.
  - ., 1985-1986. (Box 73, Folder 5)
    48th International Congress in NYC. 20 items.
  - ., 1986. (Box 73, Folder 6)
    49th International Congress Speech. 12 pages and 1item.
  - ., 1986. (Box 73, Folder 7)
    49th International Congress in Hamburg. 2 pages and 3 items.
  - ., 1986-1987. (Box 73, Folder 8)
    50th International Congress in Lugano. 29 pages and 7 items.
  - ., 1988. (Box 73, Folder 9)
    52nd International Congress Speech. 3 pages.
  - ., 1987-1988. (Box 73, Folder 10)
    52nd International Congress in Seoul. 111 pages and 14 items.
  - ., 1989. (Box 110, Folder 2)
    Salman Rushdie Affair articles. 111 items.
  - ., 1985-2003. (Box 298, Folder 11)
    Correspondence. 37 items.
  - ., 1998-2003. (Box 298, Folder 12)
    Correspondence with Michael Roberts. 14 items.
  - ., 1988-1997. (Box 298, Folder 13)
    Correspondence with Karen Kennerly. 7 items.
  - ., 1988. (Box 298, Folder 14)
    Letter to Zbigniew Herbert. 2 pages.
  - ., 1987 August 2. (Box 298, Folder 15)
    Letter to Alex Blokh. 1 page.
  - ., 1988. (Box 298, Folder 16)
    Letter from Niccolo Tucci to Karen Kennerly. 4 pages.
  - ., 1989 June 6. (Box 298, Folder 17)
    Telegram from Norman Mailer. 1 page.
  - ., 1986 August 20. (Box 298, Folder 18)
    Letter from Karen Kennerly to Barbara P. Solomon. 2 pages.
  - ., 1988. (Box 298, Folder 19)
    Letters regarding Hans Blunck. 3 pages.
  - ., 1986 January 12. (Box 298, Folder 20)
    Letter to George Shultz. 4 pages.
  - ., 1989 February 20. (Box 298, Folder 21)
    Public letter to President Bush. 1 page.
  - ., 1999 October 1. (Box 298, Folder 22)
    Defending Artistic Freedom in New York. 5 pages.
  - ., 1985. (Box 298, Folder 23)
    Campaign to Free Irina Ratushinskaya. 17 pages.
  - ., 1979, 1987-2002. (Box 298, Folder 24)
    Letters signed. 57 items.
  - Accession 2012
    - ., 1965. (Box 346, Folder 14)
      Black binder labeled "XXXIII. International P.E.N. Congress Bled-1965- Yugoslavia. Includes pencil.
    - ., 1965. (Box 346, Folder 15)
      Travel documents, receipts and tickets; includes correspondence from Sallie. 11 items.
- Series 11: Material about Susan Sontag, ca. 1960-2004
  Writings, interviews, and other press of Sontag. Arranged by type of material.
  - Sub-series 11.1, 1964-2004; 2.5 boxes (1.25 lin. ft.) and 2 oversize folders
    Writing and other non-interview press on Sontag. No arrangement.
    - ., 1974-1997. (Box 308, Folder 2)
    - ., 1988-1999. (Box 308, Folder 3)
    - ., 1966-2004. (Box 309)
      6 folders. 105 items. Includes correspondence
    - ., 1964-2003. (Box 310)
      7 folders. 101 items. Includes correspondence and 1966 article on Maria Irene Fornes
    - ., 1970-2001. (Box 311, Folder 1)
    - ., ca.1985-1999. (Box 311, Folder 2)
      4 items. Includes several photos of Sontag from Vanity Fair article research
    - ., 1971-1985. (Box 319, Folder 7)
    - ., ca. 1979, 1981. (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Sub-series 11.2, ca. 1960-2004; 10 boxes (5.00 lin. ft.) and 1 oversize folder
    Printed and recorded interviews of Sontag by others. Arranged chronologically.
    - ., 1977-2000. (Box 302, Folder 1)
      23 items.
    - ., ca. 1960-1969. (Box 320, Folder 3)
    - ., ca. 1960-1969. (Box 320, Folder 4)
    - ., ca. 1960-1969. (Box 320, Folder 5)
    - ., 1975. (Box 320, Folder 6)
      Salmagundi. 70 pages.
    - ., ca. 1970-1979. (Box 321)
      5 folders. 98 items and 60 pages.
    - ., ca. 1970-1979. (Box 322)
      6 folders. 32 items and 276 pages. Includes reel-to-reel tape
    - ., ca. 1970-1989. (Box 323)
      7 folders. 61 items and 88 pages.
    - ., ca. 1980-1989. (Box 324)
      5 folders. 73 items and 137 pages.
    - ., ca. 1980-1989. (Box 325)
      8 folders. 52 items and 246 pages. Includes photographs
    - ., ca. 1980-1999. (Box 326)
      8 folders. 107 items and 368 pages.
    - ., ca. 1990-1999. (Box 327)
      8 folders. 11 items and 833 pages. Includes Paris Review interview
    - ., ca. 1990-1999, 2000, 2003. (Box 328)
      9 folders. 11 items and 102 pages. Includes VHS tapes and audio cassettes
    - ., 2000-2004, no date. (Box 329)
      12 folders. 72 items and 273 pages. Includes early, undated interviews (some on cassette tape)
  - Sub-series 11.3, 1969-2001; 7 folders (0.25 lin. ft.)
    Material about Sontag largely created by Sontag
    - Who's Who., 1977-2001. (Box 283, Folder 10)
      24 pages and 2 items.
    - Dictionary of Literary Biography., 1997, no date. (Box 283, Folder 11)
      27 items. Includes copies of reviews and lists of articles on Sontag's work
    - Miscellaneous., 1969-2000. (Box 283, Folder 12)
      142 pages.
    - Biographies, pre-1990., no date. (Box 284, Folder 1)
    - Early Bibliographies., ca. 1969-1990. (Box 284, Folder 2)
      61 pages. Includes list of essay projects
    - Lists of Uncollected Works., no date. (Box 311, Folder 8)
    - Lists of Sontag Archive Material., no date. (Box 311, Folder 9)
      153 pages and 1 envelope.
  - Sub-series 11.4, 1996-2000; 2 folders
    Articles and correspondence relating to the Unauthorized Biography by Carl Rollyson and Lisa Paddock
    - Correspondence., 1996-1999. (Box 311, Folder 3)
      46 items.
    - Articles., 1996-1997, 2000. (Box 311, Folder 4)
  - Sub-series 11.5, 1993-2001; 3 folders
    Material relating to the Sontag Annotated Bibliography and other works compiled and edited by Professor Lee Poague
    - Conversations with Susan Sontag., 1993-1995. (Box 311, Folder 5)
      202 pages.
    - Annotated Bibliography., 1998-2000. (Box 311, Folder 6)
      160 pages.
    - Critical Response to Susan Sontag., 2000-2001. (Box 311, Folder 7)
  - Sub-series 11.6, 1967-2003; 12 folders
    Includes articles and clippings, audio interviews, and other press on Sontag.
    SUB-SERIES CONTAINS AUDIO MATERIALS: Audio materials in this collection will require assessment and possible digitization for safe access. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
    - ., 1970 August 28. (Box 341, Folder 2)
      Audio interview, Susan Sontag on the set of her film "Brother Carl." Label reads: "Sontag 5 Aug 28, 1970, Stockholm." 1 compact cassette tape; side A is empty.
    - ., 1992 October 19. (Box 341, Folder 3)
      Radio interview: "The Volcano Lover," Bookworm program hosted by Michael Silverblatt, KCRW. 1 audio CD; rebroadcast 2005 February 3 in memory of Sontag's death.
    - ., 2000 March 23. (Box 341, Folder 4)
      Radio interview: "In America," Bookworm program hosted by Michael Silverblatt, KCRW. 1 audio CD.
    - ., 2002 February 14. (Box 341, Folder 5)
      Radio interview: "Summer in Baden Baden by Leonid Tsypkin," Bookworm program hosted by Michael Silverblatt, KCRW. 1 audio CD.
    - ., 2003 February 13. (Box 341, Folder 6)
      Radio interview. Label reads: "Studio 360, Show 407 - War." 1 audio CD; includes handwritten note from Kerrie Hillman [interviewer?].
    - ., 2003 June 23. (Box 341, Folder 7)
      Audio interview, Susan Sontag in conversation with Adam Zagajewski in Tubingen, Germany. 1 audio CD; includes typed note from Nicole Bick dated 7/10/2003.
    - ., 2003 June 25. (Box 341, Folder 8)
      Susan Sontag lecture excerpt, "The Project of My Writing," at University of Tubingen, Germany. 1 audio CD.
    - ., 2003 November 27. (Box 341, Folder 9)
      Radio interview: "Where the Stress Falls," Bookworm program hosted by Michael Silverblatt, KCRW. 1 audio CD.
    - ., no date. (Box 341, Folder 10)
      Mac disk [blank?]. 1 Mac DVD-R.
    - ., 1967 April 30. (Box 346, Folder 4)
      Article clipping featuring photo of Susan Sontag and David Rieff.
    - ., 1981 March 6. (Box 346, Folder 5)
      Newspaper crossword puzzle featuring "Writer Susan."
    - ., 1981 February. (Box 351, Folder 6)
      "Susan Sontag Under Siege," New York Weekly SOHO news poster. 2 items.
- Series 12: Subject Clipping Files, no date
  Articles and clippings collected and arranged by Sontag.
  - Medicine (History of)., no date. (Box 312, Folder 1)
  - Art News., 1946 December. (Box 312, Folder 2)
  - Ratushinskaya., no date. (Box 312, Folder 3)
  - [Chiapas]., no date. (Box 312, Folder 4)
  - Camp, Retro, Etc., no date. (Box 312, Folder 5)
    12 items. Includes notes
  - Language., no date. (Box 312, Folder 6)
  - Misc. Philosophy., no date. (Box 312, Folder 7)
  - Posters., no date. (Box 312, Folder 8)
  - Gardens., no date. (Box 312, Folder 9)
  - German: Hegel, Fichte, Schelling, Lichtenberg, Lacue., no date. (Box 312, Folder 10)
  - Medicine., no date. (Box 312, Folder 11)
    26 items. Includes notes
  - Russian Art, Literature, Politics., no date. (Box 312, Folder 12)
    14 items and 1 envelope.
  - Science Fiction., no date. (Box 312, Folder 13)
  - Russian (1 of 2)., no date. (Box 313, Folder 1)
  - Russian (2 of 2)., no date. (Box 313, Folder 2)
    22 items. Note included (moved)
  - Picasso (1 of 2)., no date. (Box 313, Folder 3)
    55 items.
  - Picasso (2 of 2)., no date. (Box 313, Folder 4)
  - Marcel Duchamp., no date. (Box 313, Folder 5)
    40 items.
  - Hegel (1 of 2)., no date. (Box 313, Folder 6)
  - Hegel (2 of 2)., no date. (Box 313, Folder 7)
  - Hungarian Literature and Film., no date. (Box 314, Folder 1)
  - Medicine., no date. (Box 314, Folder 2)
    39 items and 1 envelope.
  - Darwin., no date. (Box 314, Folder 3)
  - Moon Landing., no date. (Box 314, Folder 4)
    12 items and 1 envelope.
  - Philosophy (1 of 2)., no date. (Box 314, Folder 5)
    10 pages and 17 items. Includes notes
  - Philosophy (2 of 2)., no date. (Box 314, Folder 6)
  - Levi-Strauss., no date. (Box 314, Folder 7)
  - Geology, Etc., 1969. (Box 314, Folder 8)
  - Freud., no date. (Box 315, Folder 1)
  - Freud., no date. (Box 315, Folder 2)
    9 items. Includes mostly Philip Rieff offprints
  - Freud., no date. (Box 315, Folder 3)
  - Misc. Sociology., no date. (Box 315, Folder 4)
  - Misc. Sociology., no date. (Box 315, Folder 5)
  - Misc. Sociology., no date. (Box 315, Folder 6)
    25 items. Includes letter and papers from Ivan Illich (now in Box 88, Folder 20) and notes from 1960 Susan Taubes (?) course
  - Hannah Arendt., no date. (Box 315, Folder 7)
    28 items. Includes letter from Robert Silvers (now in Box 142, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous., no date. (Box 316)
    5 folders. 138 items.
  - Miscellaneous., no date. (Box 317)
    5 folders. 120 items.
  - Communism and Intellectuals., no date. (Box 318, Folder 1)
  - Communism and Intellectuals: Gide., no date. (Box 318, Folder 2)
  - Communism and Intellectuals: Serge., no date. (Box 318, Folder 3)
  - Communism and Intellectuals: Institute Seminar., no date. (Box 318, Folder 4)
  - Communism and Intellectuals: "Intellectuals"., no date. (Box 318, Folder 5)
    34 items.
  - Communism and Intellectuals (1 of 2)., no date. (Box 318, Folder 6)
  - Communism and Intellectuals (2 of 2)., no date. (Box 318, Folder 7)
  - Communism and Intellectuals: Israti., no date. (Box 318, Folder 8)
  - Communism and Intellectuals: Censorship., no date. (Box 318, Folder 9)
    13 items and 1 folder. Includes correspondence
  - Communism and Intellectuals., no date. (Box 319, Folder 1)
  - Communism and Intellectuals: Misc. Ref. (1 of 2)., no date. (Box 319, Folder 2)
  - Communism and Intellectuals: Misc. Ref. (2 of 2)., no date. (Box 319, Folder 3)
    38 items. Includes notes and draft letter to James Fenton
  - Ballet., no date. (Box 319, Folder 4)
    73 items.
  - George Soros (OSI)., no date. (Box 319, Folder 5)
  - CCA (Montreal)., no date. (Box 319, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous., no date. (Box 320, Folder 2)
    53 items. Includes mostly items originally misfiled elsewhere in the collection
- Series 13: Material Collected by Susan Sontag, 1960-2004
  Catalogs, event programs, records, David Rieff clippings, and miscellaneous papers within the collection.
  - Event Programs and Tickets., ca. 1978-2004. (Box 46, Folder 1)
    ca. 25 items.
  - Dealer and Publisher Catalogs., 1992, 2002. (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Dealer and Publisher Catalogs., 1993, 1998-2000. (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Dealer and Publisher Catalogs., 1978, 1990-1993, 1998. (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Dealer and Publisher Catalogs., 1987-1993. (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Event Programs and Tickets., ca. 1978-2004. (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - Event Programs and Tickets., ca. 1978-2004. (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - Event Programs and Tickets., ca. 1978-2004. (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - Event Programs and Tickets., ca. 1978-2004. (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - Record Albums., 1965. (Box 163, Folder 8)
  - David Rieff., no date. (Box 163, Folder 9)
    10 items. All material found within the collection and grouped together by UCLA. Includes 3 photographs of David Rieff and Joseph Brodsky received by UCLA in William Drentell envelope
  - Miscellaneous., no date. (Box 163, Folder 10)
    14 items. All material found within the collection and grouped together by UCLA
  - Dealer and Publisher Catalogs., no date. (Box 302, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous., no date. (Box 302, Folder 3)
  - Accession 2012
    - ., no date [ca. 1970s]. (Box 350, Folder 16)
      Chinese poster displaying characters.
    - ., 1996. (Box 350, Folder 17)
      Theater program, for "La maladie de la mort" featuring Lucinda Childs.
    - ., 1985-1993. (Box 350, Folder 18)
      Article clippings, ticket stubs; includes some correspondence. Ca. 25 items.
    - ., 1960-1993, no date. (Box 350, Folder 19)
      Programs, flyers, ticket stubs, maps, article clippings, business cards and other ephemera. Ca. 75 items.
    - ., no date [ca. 1965]. (Box 351, Folder 5)
      "World-Wide General Strike for Peace" bulletin. 1 item; found in black P.E.N. conference binder, Box 346 folder 14.
- Series 14: Philip Rieff Material, ca. 1950-1995
  Manuscript material and research material of Philip Rieff, Sontag's former husband. Characterized in Access acquisition inventory as [Sontag] Teaching Material (Boxes 20 and 22).
  - ., 1991. (Box 154, Folder 1)
    Sacred Order / Social Order: Volume 1 typescript draft pages with holograph changes. 165 pages. Pages were in blue cloth three-ring binder with torn illegible label
  - ., 1985-1987. (Box 154, Folder 2)
    Sacred Order / Social Order: early typescript draft pages (varying titles) with holograph changes. 248 pages. Pages were in blue cloth three-ring binder with numeral I written on spine
  - ., 1985. (Box 154, Folder 3)
    Sacred Order / Social Order: early typescript draft pages with holograph changes. 205 pages and 1 item. Pages were in blue cloth three-ring binder with numeral III written on spine
  - ., no date. (Box 154, Folder 4)
    Research material: photocopy of The Sacred Theory of the Earth by Thomas Burnet. Folder 1 of 2. Pages 1-199. Annotated by Rieff. Pages were in blue vinyl three-ring binder with label torn off
  - ., no date. (Box 154, Folder 5)
    Research material: photocopy of The Sacred Theory of the Earth by Thomas Burnet. Folder 2 of 2. Pages 200-413. Annotated by Rieff. Pages were in blue vinyl three-ring binder with label torn off
  - ., no date. (Box 155, Folder 1)
    Research material: photocopy of texts for Bach Cantatas. ca. 190 pages. Pages were in blue cloth three-ring binder with label in back: Images in Sacred Order: the Authority of Things Not Seen
  - ., no date. (Box 155, Folder 2)
    Research material: photocopy of texts for Bach Cantatas. ca. 300 pages. Pages were in blue vinyl three-ring binder. Label in folder
  - ., no date. (Box 155, Folder 3)
    Research material: photocopy of Justice Brandeis articles. 2 items.
  - ., no date. (Box 155, Folder 4)
    Research material: photocopied essays annotated by Philip Rieff. 3 items. Pages were in blue vinyl clamp cover with label missing
  - ., no date. (Box 155, Folder 5)
    Research material: photocopied Tony Martin book, articles, messages, and database search result list. ca. 80 pages. Pages were in blue vinyl clamp cover. Label in folder
  - ., no date. (Box 155, Folder 6)
    Research material. 1 item. Pages were in blue vinyl clamp cover
  - ., 1993, no date. (Box 155, Folder 7)
    Research material: Werblowsky materials annotated by Philip Rieff; draft pages of Sacred Order / Social Order with Rieff's holograph changes. 34 pages and 4 items. Annotated by Rieff. Pages were in blue vinyl clamp cover labelled Werblowsky
  - ., 1987. (Box 155, Folder 8)
    Images of Transgression typescript draft. Pages were in blue vinyl clamp cover. Label in folder
  - ., no date. (Box 155, Folder 9)
    Research material. 1 item.
  - ., no date. (Box 155, Folder 10)
  - ., no date. (Box 156)
    Research material. 4 folders. 4 items. Articles, misc. papers and notes inserted. Annotated by Rieff
  - ., no date. (Box 157, Folder 1)
    Research material. 1 items. Article inserted
  - ., no date. (Box 157, Folder 2)
    Research material. 1 item. Articles inserted. Annotated by Rieff
  - ., no date. (Box 157, Folder 3)
    Research material. 1 item. Articles inserted
  - ., no date. (Box 157, Folder 4)
    Research material. 1 item. Article inserted. Annotated by Rieff
  - ., no date. (Box 157, Folder 5)
    Typescript draft pages with holograph changes; articles and clippings. 86 pages and 15 items. Annotated by Rieff. Pages were in blue vinyl clamp cover. Label from cover in folder as well as loose label ("Blacks")
  - ., 1993, no date. (Box 158)
    Research material. 5 folders. 7 items. Articles inserted. Annotated by Rieff
  - ., no date. (Box 159)
    Research material. 6 Folders. 6 items.
  - ., 1935-1982, no date. (Box 160)
    Research material. 7 folders. 15 items. Articles inserted. Annotated by Rieff
  - ., 1992, no date. (Box 161, Folder 1)
    Essay photocopies, correspondence. 7 items. Extra copies removed
  - ., no date. (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - ., no date. (Box 161, Folder 3)
    Research material. 2 items. Annotated by Rieff. Pages were in blue vinyl clamp cover. Label in folder
  - ., no date. (Box 161, Folder 4)